can you turn on the light Yes so I can see the
можете свет включить Да чтобы я видел
kitchen Yes yes of course a Masonic kitchen is
кухню Да да конечно масонская кухня это
always
всегда
interesting so turn the camera to the
интересно так поверните камеру на
Masonic stove here they
масонскую плиту вот кушать
cooked food
приготовили
Naro
Наро
on What are you going to tell Well what are you going to ask
на Что расскажешь Ну что спросишь
wait I can't hear I don't understand what you
подожди не слышу не понимаю что ты
're saying what are you going to tell And what
говоришь что расскажете А что
Ask Well I see you have  lag is so
Спросите Ну я смотрю у вас лаг такой
Ukrainian that you are Ukrainian yes And I see
украинский что вы украинец да А я смотрю
you have a wall covered in wallpaper you
у вас стена такая в обоях вы
wallpaper No no I am Russian
обой Да нет я русс
not Russian but some kind of
ла не русский а какой-то
Oi I am not sitting and resting No why is your
ойский не сижу отдыхаю Не а почему у вас
flag not Russian
флаг не русский
behind I can't see it well behind  Here
сзади что-то не вижу его ну сзади Вот
is your flag with
это у вас флаг такой в
spots I see this is wallpaper like this I understand And are
пятнах вижу это обои такие понял А это
you sitting at home now or
вы сейчас дома сидите или в
visiting I haven't seen how Russians have it the first time
гостях не видел как у Россиян первый раз
in roulette I've never seen how Russians have it
в рулетке никогда не видел как у Россиян
at home What furniture What interior can you
дома Какие мебель Какие интерьер можете
show me Well, I'll show Vita  I am a Mason, a
показать Ну вот я покажу Вите я я масон
Mason, a Russian Mason Yes, I am a
масон русский масон Да я
Masonic, well, you know what Masons are,
масонской ну вы знаете что такое масоны
yes Yes, I know Freemasons Well, I am of
да Да знаю вольные каменщики Ну вот я
Masonic vision, here I am showing you my
масонского зрения вот показываю вам мою
apartment, and show me  you can
квартиру а покажите детальнее можете
go through it in more detail and show it And why exactly am I
пройтись показать А для чего именно мне
interested? I've never seen a Russian
интересно Я никогда не видел российское
home And that Russian Masonic
жилище А тем Боре российское масонское
home for Borya I'm not even interested We
жилище Мне аж интересно не сер Мы же
communicate normally
нормально общаемся
Yes,
Да
of course, I've always been interested How do the
конечно всегда интересовало Как живут
children live, they went to bed now Well, don't
дети спать легли сечас Ну вы детей не
show the children Yes, show them like this
показывайте Да покажите так как
furnishings kitchen for example everything except the
обстановка кухня например всё кроме
bedroom
спальни
can you turn on the light Yes so that I can see the
можете свет включить Да чтобы я видел
kitchen Yes yes of course a Masonic kitchen is
кухню Да да конечно коне масонская кухня
always
- это всегда
interesting so turn the camera to the
интересно так поверните камеру на
Masonic
масонскую
stove So something is wrong with your Masonic
плиту Так что-то у вас с масонской
coordination it's
координацией
a little shaky Poma sons yes
проблемка шатает немножко Пома сонс да
no here we've prepared food A  what
нет вот кушать приготовили А что А что
what what what do masons eat I'm
там что вот что масоны едят мне
interested let's see Well you
интересно давай Давайте посмотрим Ну вы
should know I don't know Well what's in the
сами должны знать я не знаю Ну что там в
mason's frying pan Well let's say now potatoes with
масона Ну допустим сейчас картошка с
sauerkraut solyanka so potatoes are
квашеной капустой солянка так картошка
not that it will only be in the summer
ещё же не это она же только летом будет
where are the potatoes from  do you have potatoes now yes
картошка откуда у вас картошка сейчас да
Wow but I always have and show me Well there
Вау но мне всегда есть а покажите Ну там
really are potatoes in your frying pan
реально картошка у вас в сковородке
Potatoes Yes Show me I don't believe it  This is
Картошка Да Покажите я не верю Это
some kind of joke This is edible you can Well
какой-то Это съедобно вы можете Ну
show that you are eating this that this is a
показать что это вы едите что это
potato
картошка
really real this and how to also become a Mason
реально вот это а как тоже стать масоном
I also want to somehow get me potatoes
Я тоже хочу чтобы как-то мне картошку
like in the
достать типа
spring This is [ __ ] awesome this is really
весной Это капец это действительно
cool yes
круто да
because we have I  I know you're talking for fun, we're
потому что у нас Я знаю ты по приколу мы
not talking for fun, I'm just surprised that
не не по приколу меня просто удивило что
you actually have potatoes,
у вас реально есть картошка у нас
for example, we don't have potatoes yet. They only bring them to us
например Нет ещё картошки У нас её
in June. Why are
привозят только в июне месяце А почему
you surprised that there are potatoes in Russia?
тебя удивил то что в России есть
Well, they don't grow yet.  it's only
картошка Ну она ещё не растёт ещё же
spring and they'll be planting it
весна её только будут садить
soon Belarus will give it to us and Belarusians
Скоро нам Белоруссия даёт а а белорусы
grow potatoes all year round sh tamm
круглый год выращивают картошку ш тамм
Yes
Да
yes yes I got it damn you ate it so deliciously that
да да понял блин вы так вкусно съели что
I even wanted to take another for me
я аж захотел Возьмите ещё за меня
Eat a piece Well, come on, a second helping,
Съешьте кусочек Ну вторую порцию давай
yes, don't
ну да не
come I won't tell you  I I do
приезжай я те не я Я вот ничего против
n't say anything against it Move I'll even feed you and give you
не говорю Переезжай я тебя даже накормлю
something to drink and don't give it Well look I'll send you
напою и не давай Ну смотри отправлю
back
обратно
Look at you with such and such  or let's do it
Смотри вот ты с таком с такой или давай
this way You show me I'll pretend that
так Ты мне покажи я сделаю вид что я вот
I'm looking forward to how I ate it too because you
я предвкушаю как я тоже это поел потому
see you ate it and now I have a
что видишь ты поел и у меня теперь сли
discharge Well, how unfair Well, I
на выделение Ну как нечестно Ну я так
understand that you're also a blogger No, I'm not a blogger I
понял ты тоже блогер Да не я не блогер Я
just come in  in chat roulette
просто вот захожу в чат рулетку
to chat after work you can show
пообщаться после работы можете показать
this potato I want to enjoy its view
эту картошку Я хочу насладиться её видом
Let's communicate normally
Давайте же нормально общаемся
Damn well now
Блин ну сейчас
Damn it looks so delicious you can
Блин она так вкусно выглядит можете за
eat it for me
меня её съесть
too Eat for me you for yourself now
тоже Съешьте за меня вы за себя с теперь
for
за
me And why do you have a Ukrainian flag
меня А почему у тебя украинский флаг
now  I can ask this because
сейчас вот можно так спросить потому что
I am from Ukraine
я из Украины
look that in Russia there are no toilets and
смотрите что в России нету унитазов и
washing machines it is
стиральных машин это
true yes we are on the
правда да мы на
street
улицу
really What are you What did you believe Well yeah well
реально Ты что Ты что поверил Ну да ну у
they showed on TV that you have
нас показывали по телевизору что у вас
wooden toilets on the
деревянные туалеты на
streets we have a toilet from
улицах у нас унитаз с
America  Well
Америки Ну
how did you
как
live not me these these these these these adj I
прожи не я те это это ту это прил Я
saw we had a program Yes the journalists
видел у нас была передача Да журналисты
showed I'll show you now I'll show you
показывали покажу сейчас я тебе покажу
now it can't
сейчас не может
be Seriously this is
быть Серьёзно это прикол
some kind of joke
какой-то
seriously Look at these American toilets
серьёзно Смотри вот американские унитазы
And it flushes Well it
А он он сливает Ну он
works Show that it works press so that the
рабочий Покажи что он рабочий нажми
water flows Show Water show water
чтобы вода стекла Покажи Воду воду
and show that it really flushes or is it
а покажи что оно сливает реально или это
a fountain Just take Throw something in the
фонтанчик Просто возьми Кинь что-то в
toilet and flush so that it
унитаз и слей чтобы оно
flushes this I don't flush this  fountain
слила это не сливаю это фонтанчик
decorative toilet take Throw something in there
декоративный унитаз возьми Кинь туда
and flush show what's in there come on take some
что-то и слей покажи что там давай взял
paper and Show show so I can
бумагу и Показывай показывай чтобы я
see how it flushes show show don't
видел как она смывается показы показы не
see matchmaker
види сват
Come on let it fill up Yeah well because
Давай пусть наполнится Да ну потому что
I know this joke is there Russians buy
я знаю этот прикол есть русские покупают
decorative toilets they don't flush
декоративные унитазы они не смывают
because there is no sewerage it's
потому что нет канализаци это
a fountain
фонтанчик
come on Yes it's filling up now these are
давай Да сейчас наполняется это же
your toilets Yes come on Alexey Well show me
ваши унитазы Да давай Алексей Ну покажи
for real Well press something for a long time
реально А ну нажимай что-то долго долго
press for a long time but show me so I can see Show me on
нажима но покажи чтобы я видел Покажи в
camera So I can see that it's going to drain
камеру Да чтобы я видел что оно сольёт
Yes it hasn't filled up yet  so it
Да он ещё пока не набрался так он
leaks
протекает
no yes Well, show me
нет да А ну покажи ещё
again Well, come on, drain, drain, no
раз А ну давай сливай сливай не
merges see this is a decorative
сливается видишь это декоративный
toilet And how much does it take to collect that it takes 2 days
унита А сколько он набирает что 2 дня
No 5
надо Нет 5
minutes 5 minutes in the summer to stand with you
минут 5 минут в лете стоять с тобой
minutes Hello Meet my wife yes
минут Здравствуйте Познакомьтесь жену да
yes let's give Hello Yes let's give Give me
да давай дам Здравствуйте Да дайте Дайте
my wife I'll talk to my wife talk yes let's
жену я поговорю с женой поговори да
talk
поговорим
normally Nastya I don't want Yes
нормально Насть на хочу Да
I say Turn Turn the camera on the wife
говорю Поверни Поверни камеру на жену
Turn the camera on the wife I'll look wife is
Поверни камеру на жену я посмотрю жена
normal Nastya Show your face I don't
нормально Насть Покажи лицо не
want to tell her that this is a normal person from
хочу скажи что это нормальный человек из
Ukraine listen Tell
Украины слушай
her that this is a normal person from
Скажи ей что это нормальный человек из
Ukraine nanu got it tell Tell your wife that
Украины нану понял скажи Скажи жене что
this is a normal person from Ukraine
это нормальный человек с Украины с ним
you can
можно
talk to him  By the way Nastya is a
поговорить Да кстати Насть на это
normal person from Ukraine. I don't
нормальный человек с Украины сни Я не
want to. I just eat. Porus. I don't want to either.
хочу я кушаю просто Порус Я тоже не хочу
I said. And
я сказа А покажи
show me.
ла по Пока покажи что она кушает мне
Bye. Show me what she eats. I'm interested in what my wife eats. Well, what? Well, I'll
интересно что жена кушает Ну чем же Ну я
show you. And I don't believe it. Well, maybe.  she Well I
тебе показ А я не верю Ну может она Ну я
want to see the portions show me what she
порции хочу посмотреть покажи что же она
has leave
есть отстань от
me alone you see I'll eat calmly she has a portion
меня видишь я поем спокойно у неё порция
And what is her small portion
А что она маленькая порция
I have a question for you and you wait
та у меня тебе вопрос а ты подожди
Why why does she have a small portion
Почему почему у неё маленькая порция
take add a little more potatoes Well,
возьми доложи ещё немножко картошки Ну а
she
то она мало
took so little that it's a pity for the wife potatoes me
взяла что жалко для жены картошку меня
te
те
and how about
а как
Len wait
Лен подожди
wait chu now
подожди чу у тебя теперь
ask you with the general Why
спросить с общ Почему
not like
не как
you again  show me your wife again show me your
ты ещё раз покажи ещё раз жену Покажи
wife again she is very
ещё раз жену она очень
violent I will tell you about Zelensky yes
буйна я скажу про Зеленского да
to na na he answer you I don't want
к на на он тебе ответи я не хочу
Kun I
Кунь
want She says she doesn't want to communicate tell her
хочу Она говорит не хочет общаться скажи
tell her what tell her what let her eat and
скажи что скажи что пусть она кушает и
tell her that I am from Czechoslovakia I am not
скажи что я из Чехословакии я не
Ukrainian Listen  Yeah, listen, what do you really
украинец Слыш Да ты слышь а ты реально
have to do with this? Well, I
какое это отношение имеешь Ну по флагу я
can see from the flag. And what do I mean, and
вижу А я что а твоё
who are yours? Well, your
кто Ну твоя
position? Look, Alexey, look, I dont
позиция Смотри Алексей смотрите я не
support Zelensky or Poroshenko,
поддерживаю ни Зеленского ни Порошенко
Im on my own. Let me talk to your
никого я сам за себя Дайте я с вашей
wife. Tell me, tell your wife that
женой поговорю Скажите скажите жене что
I  from Czechoslovakia I'm not from
я из Чехословакии Я не из
Ukraine Yes, she didn't understand at all
Украины Да она поняла не вообще Вот
Tell me, did I just hang a flag like that
скажите я просто повесил флаг такой
for Ukraine No, I'm from  Czechoslovakia I am from
чтобы Украины Нет я из Чехословакии Я из
Czechoslovakia Tell your wife that I am from
Чехословакии Скажите жене что я из
Czechoslovakia Ukraine
Чехословакии Украи
This is the flag of my city in Czechoslovakia the
Это флаг моего города в Чехословакии
city of Brno this is such a flag it just
город Брно это такой флаг он просто
coincides with your country Ukrainian and the
совпадает у страны твоей украинской и
flag of the city of Brno well let her really I am from
флаг города Брно ж дайте ей реально я из
Chicho
чихо
words and show me or are you tired of it already
слова а по покажите или же надоела уже
show me or  I'm
покажите или же
tired of Nastya for a few words
надоела Насть на пару слов
on Tell her that I'm
на Скажите ей что я
Czech Nastya well talk tell her that I
Чех Насть ну поговори скажите что это я
don't want this for trolling Nastya come here No I don't
троллинга не хочу Насть иди сюда Да не
want to I said Don't want to say no well you
хочу я сказал Не хочешь скажи не ну ты
you should as a
ты должен как
man you as a man should her Look
мужчина ты как мужчина должен её Смотри
you as a man  I have to
ты как мужчина должен
change her, she
её переу она с
talks to Russians, okay, look, I'm
русскими разговаривает ладно смотри я
from Belgorod, I'll tell you, I'm from
сам с Белгорода я тебе скажу Я с
Belgorod, I hang the Ukrainian flag to
Белгорода Я вешаю украинский флаг чтобы
see who's a traitor in Russia, you
смотреть кто у нас в России есть
know, I
предатель который пожи понимаешь я их
find them, and I'm from
нахожу а я сам из
Belgorod, but I can't tell you about you.  what are
Белгорода да по тебе я не скажу то что
you a traitor tell me Tell your wife that I'm from
ты предатель скажи Скажи жене что я из
Belgorod I just
Белгорода Я просто так
hung up the
повесил
ri
ри
lazhi Give your wife the headphones I'll put them away don't
лажи Дай жене наушники я уберу не
wait if you rip it off I
подожди если ты сорвёшь егос я
see
Видишь
Look what
Смотри что
it is Show what your wife is eating look
это Покажи что жена ест на смотри
for now the intrigue remains the question of
пока интригой осталася вопрос а
whether the toilet is full by the end of the
наполнился ли унитаз всё-таки до конца
conversation or not put a plus if you
разговора или нет поставьте плюс если
think the toilet is full and
считаете что унита наполнился а минус
put a minus in  comments If the toilet
поставьте в коментах Если унита
fills up only tomorrow he once a day
наполнится только завра он раз в день
svae letter on my Telegram right now
свае пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube Zaga
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams that for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you  ma operational connection is written right
тоб ма оперативный звязок пишиться прямо
now and Popik there in telegram okrim video
зараз а Попик там в телегра окрим вдео
also interesting and useful information and we are
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и ми
sorry with you trimati constant
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational connection
оперативный звязок
independently in that  I'll show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write ah
пиши ah